Guide to the Levy Dime Novel Collection 1821-1968 Levy
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Misc. Addenda
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XI, no. 277 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: November 14, 1882 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXIII, no. 592 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: November 27, 1888 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XIII, no. 325 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 16, 1883 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XI, no. 274 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 24, 1882 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XIX, no. 483 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 26, 1886 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXIII, no. 581 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 11, 1888 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XV, no. 371 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 2, 1884 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XIX, no. 478 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 21, 1886 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XIII, no. 322 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 25, 1883 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXIII, no. 580 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 4, 1888 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XI, no. 267 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 5, 1882 (Box 125, Folder 2410)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXVIII, no. 715 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: April 7, 1891 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXXIX, no. 996 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: August 25, 1896 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXV, no. 646 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: December 10, 1889 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XL, no. 1021 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: February 16, 1897 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XLIII, no. 1098 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: February, 1900 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XL, no. 1017 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: January 19, 1897 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XL, no. 1015 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: January 5, 1897 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXV, no. 650 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: January 7, 1890 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXIV, no. 607 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: March 12, [year unknown], undated (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXXVI, no. 922 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: March 26, 1895 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XL, no. 1024 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: March 9, 1897 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXXIV, no. 879 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: May 29, 1894 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXXIII, no. 853 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: November 28, 1893 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXIX, no. 742 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 13, 1891 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXV, no. 632 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 3, 1889 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XXVII, no. 685 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 9, 1890 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Half Dime Library Series Number: vol. XLIV, no. 1105 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September, 1900 (Box 125, Folder 2411)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. V, no. 53 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: January 19, 1885 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. XXV, no. 316 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: January 29, 1890 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. VI, no. 74 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: June 10, 1885 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. VI, no. 73 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: June 3, 1885 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. XXV, no. 322 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: March 12, 1890 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. V, no. 62 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: March 18, 1885 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. II, no. 18 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: May 14, 1884 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. XVIII, no. 228 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: May 23, 1888 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. VIII, no. 96 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: November 11, 1885 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. XXIII, no. 299 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 2, 1889 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. VIII, no. 94 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 28, 1885 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. XXIV, no. 303 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: October 30, 1889 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Series Title: Beadle's Pocket Library Series Number: vol. XXXV, no. 454 City: New York Publisher: Beadle and Adams Date: September 21, 1892 (Box 125, Folder 2412)
  - Title: Better late than never Date: undated (Box 125, Folder 2413)
  - Series Title: Bow Bells Series Number: vol. XI, no. 284-vol. XII, no. 287 Date: January 5-26, 1870 (Box 125, Folder 2414)
  - Series Title: Bow Bells Series Number: vol. XXXII, no. 814 Date: undated (Box 125, Folder 2414)
  - Series Title: Bow Bells Series Number: vol. XXXII, no. 817 Date: undated (Box 125, Folder 2414)
  - Series Title: Bow Bells Series Number: vol. XXXII, no. 825-828 Date: undated (Box 125, Folder 2414)
  - Series Title: Bow Bells Series Number: vol. XXVII, no. 689-692 Date: November, 1877 (Box 125, Folder 2414)
  - Series Title: Bow Bells Series Number: vol. XXXIX, no. 989-992 Date: September, 1883 (Box 125, Folder 2415)
  - Author: Conway, John R. Title: Bowery Billy's vacation or, the bootblack detective's double-play Series Title: Bowery Boy Library Series Number: 54 City: New York Publisher: The Winner Library Co. Date: October 27, 1906 (Box 126, Folder 2416)
  - Title: Mystic Island; or, the tale of a hidden treasure Series Title: Brave and Bold Series Number: 98 City: New York Publisher: Street & Smith Date: November 5, 1904 (Box 126, Folder 2417)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 29, 46, 118, 123, 139, 153, 156, 162 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1880-1881 (Box 126, Folder 2418)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 175, 185, 215-216, 219, 233-234 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2419)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 240-241, 248-250, 260-261 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2420)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 269-270, 276-277, 281, 290 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2421)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 303-304, 307-309 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2422)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 315, 333-335 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2423)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 339-344 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2424)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 345-349 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2425)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 352, 361-363, 367 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1883 (Box 126, Folder 2426)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 374, 377, 383, 391-393 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: 1884 (Box 126, Folder 2427)
  - Series Title: The Brookside Library Series Number: 394-396, 406-407 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Format: also contains two unknown numbers Date: 1884 (Box 126, Folder 2428)
  - Title: Buffalo Bill's desperate mission; or, the round-up in Hidden Valley Series Title: New Buffalo Bill Weekly devoted to far west life Series Number: 78 City: New York Publisher: Street & Smith Date: March 7, 1914 (Box 126, Folder 2429)
  - Series Title: Cassell's Illustrated Family Paper Series Number: vol. VIX -- new series City: London Publisher: Cassell, Petter, and Galpin Format: hard cover Date: 1864 (Box 126, Folder 2430)
  - Series Title: Cassell's Illustrated Family Paper Series Number: vol. III, no. 62-vol. IV, no. 111 City: London Publisher: Cassell, Petter, and Galpin Format: hard cover Date: 1866-1867 (Box 126, Folder 2431)
  - Author: Raymond, George S. Title: The plague of the Marseilles: herdsman of the Black Mountains Series Title: The Novelette Series Number: 127 City: Boston Publisher: Office American Union, Flag of our Union, and Ballou's Monthly Date: undated (Box 127, Folder 2432)
  - Series Title: The Young Ladies' Journal an illustrated magazine Series Number: 213-222 Date: 1868 (Box 127, Folder 2433)
  - Series Title: The Young Ladies' Journal an illustrated magazine Series Number: 223-234 Date: 1868 (Box 127, Folder 2434)
  - Title: A charming child Date: undated (Box 127, Folder 2435)
  - Series Title: The Corsair a gazette of literature, art, dramatic criticism, fashion and novelty Series Number: vol. I, no. 32 City: New York Date: October 19, 1839 (Box 127, Folder 2436)
  - Series Title: The Cottage Hearth Series Number: vol. XIII, no. 4-5 City: Boston Publisher: The Cottage Hearth Company Date: 1887 (Box 127, Folder 2437)
  - Series Title: The Cottage Hearth Series Number: vol. XIII, no. 7-11 City: Boston Publisher: The Cottage Hearth Company Date: 1887 (Box 127, Folder 2437)
  - Series Title: The Deadwood Dick Library Series Number: vol. IV, no. 49-51 City: New York Publisher: M. J. Ivers & Co. Date: February, 1900 (Box 127, Folder 2438)
  - Series Title: DeMorest's Family Magazine Series Number: vol. XXXI, no. 12 City: New York Date: October, 1895 (Box 127, Folder 2439)
  - Series Title: Detective Library the only library containing true stories of the James boys Series Number: vol. I, no. 718 City: New York Publisher: Frank Tousey Date: August 28, 1896 (Box 127, Folder 2440)
  - Author: Norris, Charles Title: Messenger Frank; or, a matter of ten thousand dollars Series Title: Do and Dare Weekly a favorite weekly of young America Series Number: 48 City: New York Publisher: Street & Smith Date: January 12, 1901 (Box 127, Folder 2441)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday a journal of choice reading selected from foreign current literature Series Number: vol. I, no. 6-7, 12, 23 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1866 (Box 127, Folder 2442)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday a journal of choice reading selected from foreign current literature Series Number: vol. IV, no. 97-98, 100 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1867 (Box 127, Folder 2442)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday a journal of choice reading selected from foreign current literature Series Number: vol. VIII, no. 196, 202 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1869 (Box 127, Folder 2442)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday: a journal of choice reading Series Number: New Series -- vol. I, no. 13; vol. II, no. 38, 41-42, 46-51 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1872 (Box 127, Folder 2443)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday: a journal of choice reading Series Number: vol. III, no. 55, 57-58, 60, 63-69 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1873 (Box 127, Folder 2444)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday: a journal of choice reading Series Number: vol. III, no. 71-74, 76-78 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1873 (Box 127, Folder 2445)
  - Series Title: Every Saturday: a journal of choice reading Series Number: vol. III, no. 80, 83-84, 86 City: Boston Publisher: Ticknor & Fields Date: 1873 (Box 127, Folder 2446)
  - Series Title: Fame and Fortune Weekly stories of boys who make money Series Number: 1184 City: New York Publisher: Westbury Publishing Co. Date: June 8, 1928 (Box 127, Folder 2447)
  - Series Title: The Family an illustrated monthly magazine to amuse and instruct Series Number: vol. II, no. 7-12 City: New York Date: July-December, 1886 (Box 127, Folder 2448)
  - Series Title: The Family an illustrated monthly magazine to amuse and instruct Series Number: vol. III, no. 1-4 City: New York Date: January-April, 1887 (Box 127, Folder 2449)
  - Series Title: The Family an illustrated monthly magazine to amuse and instruct Series Number: vol. IV, no. 10 City: New York Date: October, 1887 (Box 127, Folder 2449)
  - Series Title: Family Herald a domestic magazine of useful information and amusement Series Number: vol. XC, no. 3124 Date: undated (Box 127, Folder 2450)
  - Series Title: Family Journal Series Number: 122 City: New York Publisher: International News Company Date: undated (Box 127, Folder 2451)
  - Title: Dorothy's probation Series Title: Family Journal Date: undated (Box 127, Folder 2451)
  - Series Title: The Family Magazine or weekly abstract of general knowledge Series Number: vol. I City: New York Publisher: J. S. Redfield Format: hard cover Date: 1833-1834 (Box 127, Folder 2452)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XIII, no. 386 City: London Date: August-September, 1878 (Box 127, Folder 2453)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XVI, no. 464-476 City: London Date: February-May, 1880 (Box 127, Folder 2454)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XX, no. 572-586 City: London Date: March-June, 1882 (Box 127, Folder 2455)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXI, no. 595-602 City: London Date: August-October, 1882 (Box 127, Folder 2456)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXI, no. 587-590 City: London Date: July, 1882 (Box 127, Folder 2456)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXI, no. 603-612 City: London Date: October-December, 1882 (Box 128, Folder 2457)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXII, no. 620-629 City: London Date: February-April, 1883 (Box 128, Folder 2458)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXII, no. 630-634 City: London Date: April-May, 1883 (Box 128, Folder 2459)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXII, no. 636-637, 639 City: London Date: June, 1883 (Box 128, Folder 2459)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXIII, no. 640, 642-644, 646-649, 651, 655-658, 660-664 City: London Date: July-December, 1883 (Box 128, Folder 2460)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXIV, no. 687; vol. XXV, no. 695-700, 702-705, 707-712 City: London Date: May, July-November, 1884 (Box 128, Folder 2461)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXVI, no. 723-742; vol. XXVII, no. 744-745; vol. XXVII, no. 768-769 City: London Date: February-July, December, 1885 (Box 128, Folder 2462)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXVIII, no. 771-778, 780-789 City: London Date: January-May, 1886 (Box 128, Folder 2463)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXI, no. 868; vol. XXXII, no. 882, 884, 886-894; vol. XXXIII, no. 916-919 City: London Date: November, 1887; February-May, October-November, 1888, 1887-1888 (Box 128, Folder 2464)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXIV, no. 927-938, 960; vol. XXXV, no. 966 City: London Date: January-March, August, October, 1889 (Box 128, Folder 2465)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXVI, no. 979-1004 City: London Date: January-June, 1890 (Box 128, Folder 2466)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXVII, no. 1005-1030 City: London Date: July-December, 1890 (Box 128, Folder 2467)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXVI, no. 979-982; vol. XXXVII, no. 1005-1013, 1018-1030 City: London Date: January, July-August, October-December, 1890 (Box 128, Folder 2468)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXVIII, no. 1036-1039, 1044-1056 City: London Date: February, April-June, 1891 (Box 128, Folder 2469)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXIX, no. 1057-1069 City: London Date: July-September, 1891 (Box 128, Folder 2470)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXIX, no. 1070-1076 City: London Date: October-Novmeber, 1891 (Box 128, Folder 2471)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XXXIX, no. 1077-1082 City: London Date: November-December, 1871 (Box 128, Folder 2472)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLIV, no. 1196-1200, 1202, 1205, 1241-1248 City: London Date: March-May, 1894; January-March, 1895, 1894-1895 (Box 129, Folder 2473)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLVI, no. 1249-1265 City: London Date: March-June, 1895 (Box 129, Folder 2474)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLVII, no. 1266-1279 City: London Date: July-October, 1895 (Box 129, Folder 2475)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLVII, no. 1280-1291 City: London Date: October-December, 1895 (Box 129, Folder 2476)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLVIII, no. 1301-1304 City: London Date: March, 1896 (Box 129, Folder 2477)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLIX, no. 1333-1334, 1340-vol. XLX, no. 1352 City: London Date: October, December 1896-February, 1897 (Box 129, Folder 2478)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. XLX, no. 1353-1356, 1359-1365 City: London Date: March-May, 1897 (Box 129, Folder 2479)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. L, no. 1366-1378 City: London Date: June-August, 1897 (Box 129, Folder 2480)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LI, no. 1379-1391 City: London Date: September-November, 1897 (Box 129, Folder 2481)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LI, no. 1392-vol. LII, no. 1413, 1418-1421 City: London Date: December, 1897-April, June, 1898, 1897-1898 (Box 129, Folder 2482)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LIII, no. 1422-1446 City: London Date: July-December, 1898 (Box 129, Folder 2483)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LIV, no. 1449-1454, 1457-1465 City: London Date: January-April, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 2484)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LIV, no. 1466-vol. LV, no. 1482 City: London Date: May-August, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 2485)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LV, no. 1483-1500 City: London Date: September-December, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 2486)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LVI, no. 1501-1513 City: London Date: January-March, 1900 (Box 129, Folder 2487)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LVI, no. 1514-1521 City: London Date: April-May, 1900 (Box 129, Folder 2488)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LVI, no. 1522-vol. LVII, no. 1532 City: London Date: June-August, 1900 (Box 129, Folder 2489)
  - Series Title: The Family Reader for at home and abroad: a journal for readers of all ages Series Number: New Series -- vol. LVII, no. 1534-1543 City: London Date: August-October, 1900 (Box 130, Folder 2490)